(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Good morning! Good afternoon! Good evening, wherever you are in the realms!
Welcome! You're watching "Now That's a Bop" on ERB TV!
I'm your host, oh-ho-ho-ho!
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of Justice!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you, lovely!
We have an excited crowd of Rosarians here! Huzzah!
And a great crew ready to bring some awesome tunes to you all! Huzzah!
We've got a massive lineup of absolute bop and a halfs.
Tonight we have a special theme. We are celebrating music from the '80s!
Make sure you folks at home, if you're enjoying the show, please let us know using the hashtag...
#ERBday2026! ERBday 2026, right up there, right up there!
Okay, let's get started with our first bop. Here we go. Are you ready?
It's Flyday Chinatown!
It's so Fly-day, Fly-day Chinatown
真夜中の人ごみに
In the midnight crowd
It's so Fly-day, Fly-day Chinatown
はじけるネオンサイン
The neon signs pop
肩にぶつかる外人
A foreigner bumps into my shoulder,
ウインクを投げる
and throws a wink.
知らん顔のあなた
You pretend not to notice,
…のあなた
...you
とまどいのひとコマ
A moment of confusion
踊り疲れていても
Even if I'm tired of dancing,
朝まで遊ぶわ
I'll play until morning,
港の見える場所で
In a place where we can see the harbor,
何か飲みたいのよ
I want to drink something
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
ジャスミンに口づけを
Kiss the jasmine
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I'm a foreigner too, aren't I?
お店に並ぶ金の
The gold...
ドレスを指差す
...dresses lined up in the store, I point to them
渋い顔のあなた
With your sour face,
わがままが言いたい
I want to be selfish
愛想笑いのおばさん
The lady with the fake smile,
きっと似合うわと
says they will surely look good on you...
どこか静かな場所で
In some quiet place,
着替えてみたいのよ
I want to try changing into them
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
絹ずれの月あかり
The rustle of silk in the moonlight
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I'm a foreigner too, aren't I?
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
ジャスミンに口づけを
Kiss the jasmine
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I'm a foreigner too, aren't I?
男のコになりたい
I want to become a boy
投げキッス パン
Throw a kiss, bang!
男のコになりたいのよ 私
I want to become a boy, you see
星のハイウェイ バイク飛ばし
Speeding my bike down the highway of stars...
海へ
...to the sea
アイツの後を
Following behind him,
つけて行くのさ
I'm trailing along,
そして夢を 聞きたい
and I want to hear his dreams
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is fine,
リボンをほどいて
untie my ribbon
男のコにさせといて
and let me be a boy,
朝まで一緒ね
together until the morning
だけど chance
But chance,
いつか chance
someday chance,
二人 dance する時に
when the two of us dance,
ふいに女にもどるの
suddenly I return to being a woman
投げキッス パンパンパンパン
Throw a kiss, bang bang bang bang!
男のコになりたいのよ 私
I want to become a boy, you see
世界中を自由に旅
To travel freely all around the world...
したい
...is what I want to do
パラソル一本
With just a single parasol...
飾るステッキで
...and a decorative cane,Safe to say
最後の日を決めるの
I'll decide on my final day
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is fine,
すべてをかなえて
make all my wishes come true,
女の子は見せない
I won't show the girl in me,
素顔が見たいの
I want to see your true face
そして chance
And then chance,
いつか chance
someday chance,
二人 dance する時に
when the two of us dance,
あいつ好みのミニになりそう
I feel like I'll become just his type
Be pop a lula
Be-Bop-A-Lula
Be my baby
Be pop a lula
Be-Bop-A-Lula
Be my baby
Sweet couple Pi! Pi! Woo be popple Pi! Pi!
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is fine,
リボンを解いて
untie my ribbon,
男のコにさせといて
and let me be a boy,
朝まで一緒ね
we'll be together until morning.
だけど chance
But there's a chance,
いつか chance
someday a chance,
二人 dance する時には
when the two of us dance,
ふいに女にもどるの
I'll suddenly return to being a girl.
Sweet couple Pi! Pi! Woo be popple Pi! Pi!
うぅ... うぅ...
Ooh... ooh...
なつかしい
A nostalgic...
痛みだわ
...pain,
ずっと前に
that I had forgotten...
忘れていた
...long ago.
でもあなたを
But when I...
見たとき
...saw you,
時間だけ後戻りしたの
only time turned back.
「幸福？」と
Don't ask me...
聞かないで
...\"Are you happy?\"
嘘つくのは
Because I'm not very good...
上手じゃない
...at lying.
友だちなら
I have friends,
いるけれど
I suppose,
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
but I can't burn for them like that.
失った
Why is it...
夢だけが
...that only lost dreams...
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
...look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った
The kindness...
優しさも
...that passed us by,
今は
is now...
甘い記憶
...a sweet memory.
SWEET MEMORIES
Don't kiss me baby
we can never be
So don't add more pain
Please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many nights
Thinking of you
longing for your touch
I have once loved you so much
I once loved you so much.
あの頃は
Back then we were...
若すぎて
...far too young,
悪戯に傷つけあった二人
we hurt each other in our mischief.
色褪せた
Even the faded...
哀しみも
...sadness...
今は
...is now...
遠い記憶
...a distant memory.
SWEET MEMORIES
La la la...
失った
Why is it...
夢だけが
...that only lost dreams...
美しく...
...look so beautiful?
見えるのは何故かしら
Why is it that they look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った
Even the kindness...
優しさも今は
...that passed by is now...
甘い
...a sweet...
記憶
...memory.
SWEET MEMORIES
Ah...
Mmm...
Ooh...
Ah...
You are watching ERB TV!
Brilliant, Sora! That was a masterclass in elegance.
My heart is still melting, doki-doki!
Thank you! Thank you!
It was such a sweet time singing with everyone!
I get it, I get it. Sweet times, sweet memories, I see, I see. And the lovely Nerissa Ravencroft...
...you look absolutely smashing tonight!
Oh Liz, you're such a flatterer.
I was watching from the wings, and I couldn't stop humming along.
Oh, I have a question for you guys! So if you two formed a unit, what would your name be? Something flashy for the '80s charts!
Well...
We have something in common, don't we? Blue!
And you're kind of legendary, and I'm a demon, so... how about...
...Blue Megamisama?
Blue... Blue Megamisama!
Ooh, I like that! I like that a lot! Wow, Blue Megamisama!
Beautiful! So cool!
Sora, here's a question for you. We all know you are an idol, but tonight you look like a movie star.
A movie star! Which '80s movie would you want to star in?
Oh... E.T.!
E.T.!
Oh, that's a good one! That's a good one! Yeah, yeah, yeah! I'll get my bike and you can hop in my basket, yeah? Oh my god!
Nerissa, question for you! You've got a powerful voice, yes.
What is your favorite powerful band from the '80s?
I don't know if I'd call them powerful, but you know the answer before I even say it.
The Smiths!
Yes, I know you enough that I already knew the answer. Classic!
But that's still a great answer! Yes, yes, yes. All right!
Okay, I better get off and get ready for the next wild track. Yes, wild!
I'll leave you guys to it. Ta-ra, loves, ta-ra!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
You are watching ERB TV!
All right then, let's move on to the next song, darlings.
One, two...
Cobra! Huzzah!
コブラ
作詞：冬杜花代子　作曲：大野雄二
[Song: Cobra]
[Lyrics: Kayoko Fuyumori / Music: Yuji Ohno]
街をつつむ
Wrapping the city...
Midnight fog
孤独なシルエット
A lonely silhouette,
動きだせば
once it starts to move...
それは 紛れもなく
That is, without a doubt...
ヤツさ
...him!
コブラ
Cobra!
Leaving me blue, コブラ
Leaving me blue, Cobra!
コブラ... Only memories after you
Cobra... Only memories after you...
背中に まとわりつく 陰りは
The shadow that clings to my back...
男という名の 物語
...is a story called 'man'.
許されるはずもない Peace and Love
There's no way it'll be forgiven, Peace and Love.
空をよぎる サイレント
Crossing the sky silently...
抑えた バイオレット
...a restrained violet.
うす汚れた日々
In these dirty days...
ひとり闇を歩む 奴さ
...he's a guy who walks through the darkness alone.
コブラ Leaving me blue
Cobra, leaving me blue...
コブラ Missing you true
...Cobra, missing you true...
コブラ Only memories after you
...Cobra, only memories after you.
ハートに 刻まれた あの日は
That day carved into my heart...
ロマンと呼ぶには 熱すぎて
...was too hot to be called romance.
巡り来る はずもない Peace and Love
There's no way it'll return, Peace and Love.
IT'S LOVE / 作詞：岩佐友晴 作曲：野下俊哉
[Song: IT'S LOVE / Lyrics: Tomoharu Iwasa / Music: Toshiya Noshita]
周りにいつも男たち
There are always men...
取り巻いてて まるで君はビーナス
...surrounding you; you are just like Venus.
ついに落としたミラクルさ
I finally pulled off a miracle...
砂漠の中から見つけだしたジュエル
...and found a jewel in the middle of the desert.
迎えに行くよ どんなときも
I'll come to pick you up, no matter when...
振り回されても Drastic & Crazy for you
...even if you lead me on, I'm drastic & crazy for you.
形の見えない 繋がりを
An invisible connection...
信じたい Eye to Eye
...I want to believe in it, eye to eye.
時には確かめ合いたいよ
Sometimes I want us to confirm it with each other...
Don't you know, no, no, IT'S LOVE
小麦色した君の肌
Your wheat-colored skin...
やたらソフィスティケイト アクション 高すぎるよテンション
...your sophisticated actions, my tension is way too high.
会えない夜は目の下に
On nights we can't meet, under my eyes...
黒いエニグマがシャドウを塗りに来る
...a black enigma comes to paint shadows.
違う匂いじゃ 火がつかない
A different scent won't light my fire.
Steal you, Smile you, まとめてマインドジャック
Steal you, smile you, wrapping it all up as a mind jack.
形の見えない 繋がりで
Through an invisible connection...
感じたい Heart to Heart
...I want to feel it, heart to heart.
時には確かめ合わなくちゃ
Sometimes we have to confirm it with each other...
Don't you know, no, no, IT'S LOVE
カサブランカが素顔に戻るとき
When the Casablanca lily returns to its true self...
宵闇の涙も見せて 折り取りに
...show me your twilight tears as I pluck you.
離さない 離れない このままいつまでも
I won't let go, I won't leave, just like this forever...
時を重ねていこう そしていつか Come together
...let's make time pass together, and someday come together.
形の見えない 繋がりを
An invisible connection...
信じたい Eye to Eye
...I want to believe in it, eye to eye.
時には確かめ合いたい
Sometimes I want us to confirm it...
...Don't you know, don't you know, no, no
かたちの見えない繋がりで感じたい
I want to feel our invisible connection
Heart to heart
ときには確かめ合うのもいいじゃない
Isn't it fine to make sure of it sometimes?
Don't you know, don't you know, no, no
It's love
You are
watching
ERB TV
恋におちて -Fall in love-
[Song: Fall in love]
もしも願いが叶うなら
If my wishes could come true
吐息を白いバラに変えて
I'd change my sighs into white roses
逢えない日には 部屋じゅうに
On the days I can't meet you, all over the room...
飾りましょう
...let's decorate them
貴方を想いながら
While thinking of you
Darling, I want you
逢いたくて
I want to see you
ときめく恋に 駆け出しそうなの
I feel like running into a heart-throbbing love
迷子のように 立ちすくむ
Standing still like a lost child...
わたしをすぐに 届けたくて
...I want to reach you immediately
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number but stopped my hand
I'm just a woman
Fall in love
If my wishes can be true
Will you change my sighs
To roses, whiter roses
Decorate them for you
Thinkin' 'bout you every night
And find out where I am
I am not
Livin' in your heart
Darling, I need you
どうしても
No matter what
口に出せない願いがあるのよ
There is a wish I just can't say out loud
土曜の夜と日曜の
Because on Saturday nights and Sundays...
貴方をいつも欲しいから
...I always want you
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number but stopped my hand
I'm just a woman
Fall in love
Darling, you love me
今すぐに
Right now...
貴方の声が 聞きたくなるのよ
...I want to hear your voice
両手で 頬を 押さえても
Even if I hold my cheeks with both hands
途方に暮れる 夜が嫌い
I hate the nights I spend feeling lost
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number but stopped my hand
I'm just a woman
Fall in...
Don't you remember
When you were here
Without a thinking
We were caught in fire
I've got a love song
But...
Three loving hearts are pullin' apart of one
Three loving hearts are pulling apart of one
Can't stop you
Can't hold you
Can't wait no more
I'm just a woman, Fall in love
青い水平線を
The blue horizon...
いま駆け抜けてく
...I'm running through it now.
とぎすまされた
Feeling the flow...
時の流れ感じて
...of sharpened time.
ときめきへと
Towards excitement...
動き出す世界は
...the world begins to move.
忘れかけてた
Bringing back...
遠い夢の訪れ
...a distant dream I'd almost forgotten.
Ride on time さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, if your thoughts are wandering
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
Accept them gently and wrap them up softly
Ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in my heart
あふれる喜びに 拡がれ Ride on time
Spread to the overflowing joy, Ride on time
僕の輝く未来
My shining future...
さあ回りハジメて
...is starting to turn now.
虚ろな日々も全て 愛に溶け込む
Even the empty days will all melt into love.
何という朝 今すぐ君のもと
What a morning! Right now, to your side...
届けに行こう
...I'll go to deliver...
燃える
...my burning...
心
...heart...
迷わず
...without hesitation.
Ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, start running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining, even to the point of being blinded!
Ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in my heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride on time
I'll send it to the soul taking flight, Ride on time
届けに行こう
I will go to deliver...
燃える心 今こそ
...my burning heart, now is the time!
Oh...
Ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, start running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining, even to the point of being blinded!
Ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light a fire in my heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride on time
I'll send it to the soul taking flight, Ride on time
Ride on time さまよう想いなら
Ride on time, if your thoughts are wandering
やさしく受け止めて そっと包んで
Accept them gently and wrap them up softly
Ride on time...
あふれる喜びに
To overflowing joy
拡がれ Ride On Time
Spreading, Ride On Time
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride On Time, let time run
愛よ光り出せ
Let love shine
目もくらむ程
To the point of dazzling
Ride On Time
心に火を点けて
Light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
I'll send it to your soul taking flight, Ride On Time
You're watching ERB TV!
I don't know how to dance.
Unbelievable! Are we in a 1980s high school disco?
Disco, disco! Yes, disco!
Does this uniform suit me?
Ooh, it's super cute!
You both look kawaii.
But the real question is, is the world ready for such charm?
You've captured the very heart of everyone watching... including mine!
Liz, is this mustache real?
Hey, hey! Hands off! Hands off! Hands off!
This here is top-tier Great Exgardan craftsmanship!
But... I must-ache you a question.
Ahaha!
Anyway! Korone, I heard you're a tough pooch.
Between you and Marine, who would be the leader of the school?
Now, Korone! Bring it on!
Okay, Marine! Come on!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What the frig?
Hey! Break it off! Break it off! Break it off!
This is the 80s, ladies, this is the 80s.
We settle things with a dance-off!
Dance? Dance-off?
Dance-off!
Which leads me to my next question: Who would win in a dance battle?
Anyway, anyway, I'd love to stay and chat, but I gotta dash!
Korone, Marine, please lead us into the next song! Cheers, ladies, let's go!
Okay! Okay!
Now, what is our next song?
I hear it's highly energetic!
Alright, it looks like everything's ready!
Lend me your energy! Huzzah!
Sparking!
光る 雲を突き抜け Fly Away
Shining, piercing through the clouds, Fly Away
からだじゅうに 広がるパノラマ
A panorama spreading across my whole body
顔を 蹴られた地球が怒って
The earth that was kicked in the face gets angry
火山を爆発させる
Making the volcanoes erupt
溶けた北極(こおり)の中に
In the melted ice of the North Pole
恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
If there were dinosaurs, I'd want to train them to ride a ball
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA 何が起きても気分は へのへのカッパ
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA, no matter what happens, my mood is Heno-heno-kappa
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA 胸がパチパチするほど 騒ぐ元気玉
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA, my heart is bursting, like a restless Genki-dama
元気玉... sparking!
The Genki-dama roars... sparking!
空を急降下 jet coaster
Diving through the sky on a roller coaster
coaster!
落ちてゆくよ パニックの楽園へ
I fall into a paradise of panic!
景色逆さになると愉快さ
The scenery turns upside-down and I cheer up
愉快さ
(cheer up!)
山さえお尻に見える
'Cause the mountains even look like butts!
悩む時間はないよ
There's no time for worrying,
どこかに潜む
'Cause there's a surprise hidden somewhere,
「びっくり！」に逢いたいから
And I wanna find it!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭カラッポの方が夢詰め込める
I'd rather have my head be empty, so I can stuff it with dreams!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔ウルトラ Z で
With a smile that's Ultra-Z,
今日もア イヤイヤ イヤイヤ イ
Even today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分はへのへのカッパ
No matter what happens, I feel like it's no big deal!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど
Just as loudly my heart pounds,
騒ぐ元気玉... sparking!
The Genki-dama roars... sparking!
You are watching ERB TV!
Absolutely bonkers! Standing ovation!
And round of applause for that spectacular energy!
We did it! Welcome to the desk, Nene and Iroha!
Yeah! Yeah!
リズ！
Liz!
リズ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Liz, happy birthday!
Oh yes, today is my birthday!
ハッピーバースデートゥーユー！ありがとう、ありがとう！
Happy birthday to you! Thank you, thank you!
リズ、とってもパワフルだね！
Liz, you are so powerful!
Ah yes, powerful dance, powerful singing,
And powerful pose!
Oh yeah, very powerful pose!
So cute! Cute?
ねね、So cute、リズ、ラブ！
Nene, so cute, Liz, love!
ラブ、ラブ、ラブ！ I love you too!
Love, love, love! I love you too!
ずるい！ずるい！ずるい！私も！
No fair! No fair! No fair! Me too!
ラブ、ラブ、ラブ、ラブ、ラブ！
Love, love, love, love, love!
I love you too, Iroha!
We're very powerful! So very powerful!
Everyone was so powerful!
みんなブロンドヘアーだね！
And everyone had blond hair!
Yes, blond hair is super!
Super powerful! Like Super Saiyan!
Super Saiyan level blond hair, you know? Very powerful, very powerful!
Yes! The strongest!
And I felt everyone's power!
And Nene, your energy is like a dragon!
Could you show the viewers your most powerful dragon pose?
ドラゴンポーズ！
Dragon pose!
ううう... ガオーッ！
Mmm... Rawr!
ドラゴンマウス、ガッチンガッチン！
Dragon mouth, chomp chomp!
Oh yeah, powerful pose!
かっこいい！かっこいい！
So cool! So cool!
That was incredible!
And Iroha, your focus during that dance was amazing!
Could you demonstrate your finest samurai warrior stance?
OK見てて！拙者はサムライだよ！
Okay, watch! I am a samurai!
つんつん... しゅっ...
Tun tun... swish...
ジャキーン！
Schwing!
So strong! Strong, strong samurai warrior!
You both performed in a big group tonight. There were seven of us all together on stage.
Tell me, who was the most cha-la, carefree member at rehearsals?
Who do you think was the most cha-la?
ねね先輩、リハーサル中もずっとそうだったよね。
Nene-senpai was always like that during rehearsals, too.
Congratulations! おめでとう！
Congratulations!
みんなでやろう！みんなで、あーと...
Let's do it together! Everyone, let's...
Oh, let's do it together! / Together!
Oh, yeah, okay, okay, okay.
せーの！
Ready, set...
Congratulations...
...standing ovation!
ねね先輩が一番チャラいわ！
Nene-senpai is the most flashy!
イェーイ！チャラ！チャラ！
Yay! Flashy! Flashy!
That was most cute and chara, but...
That was so cute and flashy, but...
チャラ！チャラ！
Flashy! Flashy!
That was marvelous! What a marvelous time we had! Yes!
But sadly, oh no, it's come to our last tune in it!
But sadly, oh no, it's come to our last tune!
I must prepare for the grand finale! I shall return very soon, gang!
Nene, Iroha, please keep the audience entertained for a moment. Look after them, okay?
Two of you, look after them, warriors! Okay, see you soon!
バイバイ！頑張ってー！
Bye-bye! Good luck!
さあ、今夜のスターの、リズは、一体最後に何を見せてくれるんでしょうか！
Now, what kind of final performance will tonight's star, Ryz, show us...
ね、楽しみですね！じゃあ皆さん、見るのそのままで、それでは、
We are so excited! Everyone, stay tuned just as you are, and now...
行きましょう、はい！
...let's go! Here we go!
You're watching ERB TV!
せーの、
Ready, set...
Huzzah!
I believe the morning sun
Always gonna shine again and
I believe a pot of gold
Waits at every rainbow's end, oh
I believe in roses kissed with dew
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
I believe in make-believe
Fairy tales and lucky charms and
I believe in promises
Spoken as you cross your heart, oh
I believe in skies forever blue
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feeling the way that I do
You can call me Pollyanna
Say I'm crazy as a loon
I believe in silver linings
And that's why I believe in you
I believe there'll come a day
Maybe it will be tomorrow
When the bluebird flies away
All we have to do is follow
I believe a dream can still come true
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feeling the way that I do
I believe in friends and laughter
And the wonders love can do
I believe in songs and magic
And that's why I believe in you
You may say I'm a fool
Feeling this way about you
There's not much I can do
I'm gonna be this way my life through
'Cause I still believe in miracles
I swear I've seen a few
And the time will surely come
When you can see my point of view
I believe in second chances
And that's why I believe in you
Hello, sweethearts! Lovely to see you, to see you... lovely!
What did you think of the first show on ERB TV?
Did you enjoy it? What did you think of the song choices?
I really hope you loved it as much as I loved performing with such amazing guests. Huzzah!
Rosarians, to arms! Are you ready...
...for the surprise?
I have something lovely to present to all of you!
Here we go... 3, 2, 1!
I have birthday merch!
First up is this!
The beautiful key visual art of this birthday merch is on a tapestry!
I'm relaxing with Bobby and a cute Rosarian after a dance workout.
Please display this wonderful retro-style tapestry and take pictures for me to see, please!
Would absolutely love to see how you decorate the room with it.
As you've visited the TV studio...
...make sure to pick up your very own ERB TV Mug.
Use it to hydrate while watching me on the telly!
Mum, I'm on ERB TV!
Hey, Mum, I'm on the telly!
I go saying that, and most likely right now, Queen Mother is watching this on the telly.
Next, you've all been wanting this, and so have I...
...a Rosarian Plushie!
Ah! I'm so freaking happy!
My adventures have been nothing without my loyal, amazing Rosarians.
Now you can have your very own Rosarian Bloodflame Kingdom powerful pooch.
I am your sword, and you are my shield.
We are powerful together.
That's right!
Next, we have a set of four pin badges!
Y'all know I love collecting pin badges.
And here's some new ones for you to collect.
We have the ERB TV logo badge, shield badge, Rosarian paw...
...and a Rosarian with a headband on saying BFK.
Bloodflame Kingdom, represent!
You all look amazing with an '80s headband on, I must say!
Lastly, I recorded another voice pack in both English and Japanese.
The voice pack is called "Exercise with Elizabeth".
So join me on our training arc as we exercise together.
Onwards and upwards!
Then, if you purchase the whole set, the full shebang, there's a full set purchase bonus.
You get a postcard with the key visual on it, but that's not all.
The limited quantity includes...
...a postcard with a handwritten signature by yours truly.
Please do not worry. Even when those run out, you still get the postcard with my replica signature.
And that is the full set of my birthday merch!
What do you think?
There's been a lot of love put into this merch...,s:
There's been a lot of love put into this merch...
...and I especially can't wait to cuddle my own Rosarian Plushie!
Well, before we wrap up, I'd like to give a special thanks to the guests.
It is an honor performing with you all.
I'll treasure these sweet memories forever.
Thank you to the crew. Amazing job, everyone!
Thank you to my dance teachers who made the choreos. I hope I made you proud with my moving and grooving!
Most of all, thank you, my beautiful kingdom, my Rosarians, for checking out my first birthday live.
First ERB TV show!
Those were some bops and a half, right?
Okay.
Make sure to eat your noms, hydrate, get good sleep...
...because we want our kingdom to be good and strong!
I love you all very much.
And most of all, let my voice be your strength.
Mwah! Bye-bye!
You're watching ERB TV!